Zhonghui Duan(Leslie)

Full Stack Web Developer

Phone number:0468911943 | Email:leslied41@gmail.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/leslie-duan-641853121/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated full stack web developer with experience building websites and web applications, focusing on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and Next.js. Dedicated and passionate to following and learning new technologies and languages, and facilitating early adoption of innovations. Enjoy problem-solving and collaborating with team members for the achievement of team goals.

Skill Set

Front-end: HTML CSS/SASS JS (ES 6+) React Next.js Typescript Tailwind Styled-component **Back-End:** Node.js Express MySql GraphQL RestApi PHP Sanity MongoDB Mongoose **Development & Deployment:** Git Github Vercel Heroku Postman Yarn Npm Figma

Testing: Jest testing-library/react Cypress Soft Skills: Creative, Teamwork, Problem-solving

Project Experience

Contemporary art gallery (Phd Group) website - Full stack developer

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

https://www.phdgroup.art/

https://github.com/leslied41/art_gallery_hk

Front-end: Next.jsBack-end: Sanity

Responsibility:

- Solo developer for the web application both front-end and back-end using Next.js and Sanity from scratch.
- Built functionality that enabled users to edit website UI and content by updating data stored in Sanity.
- Collaborated with designer to develop and update site's front end and interaction according to client's requirements.
- Created mobile responsive user experience using grid layout that allowed cross-platform accessibility to this website on any device.

CRUD app with Node, Express, and MongoDB - Full Stack developer

Feb 2022

https://premier-league-api-frontend.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/leslied41/premier_league_api_frontend https://github.com/leslied41/premier_league_api

Front-end: ReactBack-end: Node.js

Achievement:

- Implement authentication and authorization using JWT. Only admin can add, edit, delete teams in dashboard through rest api.
 - Besides CRUD, teams can be filtered, searched and sorted based on different terms.

Movable toy robot on a 5 units x 5 units square - developer

Oct 2021

https://github.com/leslied41/robot challenge

built with: vanilla javascript HTML CSS

Responsibility:

- Developed web application that can simulate a toy robot moving on a square tabletop, of dimensions 5 units x 5 units using vanilla javascript, HTML and CSS.
- Multiple robots can be added on the table and only active one can roam around the surface of the table but falling from the table be prevented.

Achievement:

- Successfully developed simulated robots that can roam on the table.
- By using CSS animation and @keyframes, simulated robots are animated.

Employment History

Electrical Engineer, Xinxiang Civil Air Defense Office

Dec 2012 - June 2019

Responsibility:

- Installed and maintained office's computer systems and network.
- Civil air defense equipment and facilities data collection and entry to database.
- Provided network technical support for civil air defense exercises and training including planning, designing, and installing networks.

Education

Self-Learning Full stack open 2021 online course

Nov 2021 - Now Online

https://fullstackopen.com/en/

Learn React, Redux, Node.js, MongoDB, GraphQL and TypeScript in one go! The main focus is on building single page applications with ReactJS that use REST APIs built with Node.js.

Self-Learning freeCodeCamp.org online learning

June 2020 - Now Online

https://www.freecodecamp.org/

Finished courses:

- Full React Course 2020 Learn Fundamentals, Hooks, Context API, React Router, Custom Hooks
- · Next.js for Beginners Full Course
- Node.js and Express.js Full Course

Master of Information&Communication Technology (ICT)

July 2019 - June 2021

University of Tasmania

• High distinction(90%) achieved in Web Development assignment

Relevant Subjects:

- KIT-502 Web Development H5, CSS, JS, PHP, MYSQL
- KIT-506 Software Development C#
- KIT-607 Mobile Application Development Swift, Flutter, Kotlin (HD achieved in programming assignment)
- KIT-712 Data Management Technology PL/SQL, SQL Tunning
 KIT-501 ICT Systems Administration Fundamentals DHCP, Linux, DNS, Subnet Masking
- · KIT717 Internet of Things and Web Applications Arduino, PHP, C

Bachelor of electrical engineering and automation

Sep 2008 - June 2012

Henan Institute of Science and Technology

Relevant Subjects:

- C Programming
- Basis of Computer